[Music]
Me [Music]
I just wanna go
with you baby you know I [Song voice]
just like to talk with you
[Music]
You don't have to tell [Song voice] me anything I [
Music] just wanna go
with [Song voice] you I just want to see
you
good evening people welcome and welcome back to
another video it's a new day so let's just say it's a
beautiful
it is 4:43 pm now and I am in Goa and
I am very excited because this is
going to be my second
solo trip in my life is it my second I mean as far as
I can remember this is my second solo
trip the first time I went to Nepal because I
wanted to attend Atif Aslam's concert
and the second time is this Goa trip and
I had booked the tickets and BNB long back
when I was in Guwahati only when
I thought that I was planning to go to Delhi just then
I booked the ticket here  Had
booked it too.  And I booked this BNB for six
days.  It cost me a bit.  I
Think It Was 3000 Per Night.  So that's it, it's a bit
expensive but I just wanted a solo trip
for myself.  I want a like me myself moment.  So
I am very happy.  I am very very
excited for the coming days.
I don't have any special plan that I will do
this or that.  I am not someone who
goes to such a tourist place and explores it, you know.
I am not that person.  My way
of having fun and a good trip is
live the slow life, go to a nice cafe, dress
up nicely, take a walk, try out restaurants.  That's it guys.
This is my kind of
fun trip.  And you want to see any tourist
places in this video.  I think.  And I am
sitting in front of Ashwin Beach.
Like 2 minutes walk to Ashwin beach.  And let me tell you all
why I am staying here.
Like why only Ashwin Beach?  I could have gone
to South Goa.  And I could also go to different beaches.
But I came to Ashwin Beach
because when I came to Goa two years ago,
I told myself that one day I am going to come here
alone.  And I will enjoy it so much.
One thing happens that we went to a
resort.  Ok?  To just have like a
watermelon juice like that.  You know I have
some pictures also.  So I'll put it here.
This is literally my core memory.  Then
I was thinking that one day I will come here.  If
I have enough money, I will come and
sit in front of the beach.  I'll just
romanticize my life.  You know I will
bring my laptop.  I will just work.  It's like, I want that
[nasal sound], I say,
just enjoy the view.  Do slow life work.   That's
my kind of life.  You know like that's what
I love.  So I am very
excited.  And this trip is going to be a
very slow trip.  I think I will
go for a walk, get a massage and that's how it will be.
Oh my food is here.  Hello, okay.  So my food
is here and I have ordered KFC.  I can
explain why.  I also thought that
why would I eat KFC after coming to Goa
but everything was very
expensive.  And KFC fell like yeah
right.  Because I have
ordered dinner along with it.  And I have spicy
ramen with me.  So I'll make that and here
Blink Kit and Instagram all this stuff does
n't work.  So I will have to you know like go for a
little walk.  And today I am a
little tired because I slept only for
three hours and travelled the whole day.  I ate
only Prinkles since morning.  So I am
going to make spicy ramen now and I am going to
enjoy it.  So let's make it together.
[MUSIC]
Good morning guys.  It's a new day.  So let's just say that it's a
beautiful day.
I'm a morning person now.  Don't Talk to Me Guys.
I'm a morning person.  I
once said that if I become a morning person
then you know like my life
is set.  And I can't believe I'm waking
up so early in a few days.  Like, for the past few days
something or the other has been happening that I have to
wake up early.  And I had a flight yesterday
and today my eyes have opened just like that.
So I am very happy.  So now I'm going to
check my neighborhood.  Let's see how it is,
what it is.  I didn't see anything
well yesterday.  And I also
see where the path to the beach leads.  It is a 2 minute
journey.  So we'll figure it out.
[Music]
Sometimes it used to be
[Music] [Song voice] How was my
friendship, my
heart wanted to say [Music] But I don't get to listen to you,
good morning guys.  It is 9:42 am and I am here
at Ashwin beach just walking and
having fun.  I feel so grateful.  I was
listening to some music and then I also
clicked some pictures.  Like I did not
find any stranger.  They clicked my photo
because I also click
their pictures.  And you know what guys.
I didn't think I would have so much
fun on a solo trip.  Like this is my
actual first day here and I feel like
so good like I already feel like I am having fun like this
and this time when I was booking the ticket
then I was
more excited than afraid because last time when
I went to Nepal alone, my first solo
trip then I was so scared and I was very
nervous that what will happen to me,
how will I enjoy, I have to
click my pictures like this but iss baar mere
ko aisa kuch bhi feel nahi hua this time I was like even if I don't have
pictures it doesn't
matter I am just going to have fun I am going to
enjoy my solo life.  I'm gonna take
selfies.  This was all there was.  But I am already
having so much fun.  I feel so grateful for
this life.  And get him out of the house.  You will
feel good.  You should notice that whenever
you are at home, whether in the house or in a room
like in your apartment, anywhere
like in a closed room, then you will feel a
lot of mental stress.  And you feel like it's not
happening.  This is not happening to
me.  You will definitely not miss all this.  But
as soon as you step out of the house, you can
literally feel
that you are overthinking and suddenly you feel like I can do this.
So get out of the house, get out of the room
and have fun.  Go for a work.
And one thing that makes me very happy is
that I have become a morning person.
What?  I am thinking like this.
I can't believe that I am going to stay here for 7 days.
And there is another reason you know why I came
to Goa.  I will be very honest with you guys,
what is there to hide from you guys.
Actually I wanted to shift cities.  I was
telling the same thing to Papa that I want to
shift cities.  I want to like go to Mumbai
or different things like that.  It happens that right now I am feeling like I want
to
explore more.  I want to make blogs but
in different cities because I have lived in Delhi a
lot.  But I don't think I will be
able to leave Delhi either.  So let's see.  So
Goa was on my list for a long time, ever since
I came to Goa for the first time, I felt that
I had to stay in the beach.
I love beaches because beaches
always like you know they do something to my
mind like I start feeling so happy and good so that was it.
But let's see,
everyone has such excitement
and happiness on the first day.  So let's see
how my 7 day trip goes and I
am looking for a breakfast spot guys.   It's
very early in the morning so no restaurants are
open.  I want to go to a cute
cafe.  I want to have sandwiches.  I Want to Have Anything
Like Breakfast at Breakfast.
I want to have bread to be very honest.
And I'll go grocery shopping too.  I'll
buy some for my BnB as I wo
n't be able to leave overnight.  Since I'm
on a solo trip.  So that's the update.  I will also
take you guys along with me.  The Wa and
Na people are cleaning the beach.  Let me show you.
Ok.  So I'm looking for [music] a
grocery store because I need to buy
some things.  I don't think I will be
able to go out in the evening.  So that's it.
[Music]
Showing 300 meters from here.  So I
love to work.  So I am just walking only.
This is close guys.  The grocery [MUSIC] store
is closed, guys.  Everything is closed.
[Music]
[Music] Do you
know what time it is, guys?
It's 12 PM and I'm done with my brunch.
I went for a walk also because I was
walking in the middle.  And this day is
feeling so long, which is so good.
Because I don't wake up early-early na.   So
today I woke up early.  So my
day seems so long to me.  Like I have the
entire day still.  And yes, I have done
some small grocery shopping.  The
bigger store was closed so
I picked up a few things from the smaller one.  Just in
case I get hungry at night, guys, I'm
still [music] not sure if
I should go out because I'm going to be a
little late coming back, so I'm scared
[music] since I'm on a solo trip.  This
is my outfit by the way it looks so good and I am also
wearing a cap.  And here so many
dog ​​people are hungry that I get very scared.
It's About to Rain Guys.  I [MUSIC] am so
scared.  I don't know why I am doing this
to myself.
I'm just walking by the beach and really
liking my outfit.
So I am looking for a dinner place and I might go there
which is behind me because
my BnB host also
recommended it.  [Music] I Really
Want Some Good Pictures or That's Why I'm
Looking for Something Girly But Then I Can't
Find Any Girls.  I'm thinking there's
a guy right here in front of me.  I am thinking
of asking him whether he will click my photo
or not.  But then he is very busy
[Music]
Working out as you guys can see
So I am here for dinner and I was having a
chill dinner But pata nahi dil mein thoda thoda dak ho raha hai Because
you know [Music]
So my one is here I was saying that I am feeling
very dirty because I have to go to my place
because
my pasta is not coming.  I had
[music] to go also.
Good morning people.  It's a new day.  So let's just say that it's a
beautiful day.
Today I did not feel like getting up.
And it has just started raining again.
Like rain comes and stops just before it stops.
So it is raining right now.  I Can See From Here
Like From a Window.  Now I am going to make
myself a cup of coffee and I will also have
bread with butter and some banana
chips.  I know early in the morning but I'm gonna have
it.  And my plan for today is to
dress up and go to eat Goan Thali.
Because I had Goan thali last time also.   It is
giving sunlight right now.  Then again, I have
eaten Goan thali before.  But then I don't really
remember the taste.  So ya but
I am
happy birthday Nikki.   Thank
you.   Thank
you.  Come on
guys, I am all ready and I feel super
pretty.  I am wearing this pretty
kaftan top.  And This Is From The Brand
Fashion Capital.  I have this Minisa bag.  It's
from MirageO.  This is out of stock.  And
I have this footwear here which I wore yesterday also.
And I will take this for you all.
It's from MTR and what else or I am
going to go to have Goan Thali.  I have
booked a taxi.  It's in more gym
because I checked and the famous Goan
thali toh do like recommendation came, I did
not like recommendation and my BNB
host also recommended this place which I am going to.
So ya oh my driver is here by.
So my thali is here.  I don't know what is in it.
I didn't do my restage.
Ok.  So let's eat.  I don't know how to eat.
This is so good.  Wow.
Oh this is so soft.   It
's good friend.
I swear guys if someone asks me for a lift
I will say yes because I am so
tired.  I've been working straight for
[music] like 20 minutes now.  But Am I
About to Reach?  It's only 4 minutes.  But since long it was
showing only 6 minutes.
I am here.  I am leaving now.
Oh my God.  I can't believe that I am
enjoying solo trip guys.  It's so fun.  And
you guys might be wondering why I am
carrying an iPad?  It's because my sister has
taken my power bank.  And I didn't want you to know
repurchase it.  So or I will ask
someone to click a picture for me because
I am feeling pretty.
Now ok ok
guys it's a new day.  So let's just say that
[music] it's a beautiful day.  I'm
on my way to have some machas.  [Music]
Yesterday, I was walking all alone down the road.
Then I Noticed [Music]
That There's a Good Matcha Place.  So I need to go there.  I
mean I want [music] to go there
because I want to have good matcha.  I wanna have
something.  It's Quiet Late Now.  It's
like afternoon.  And I haven't
eaten anything yet.  And if someone gives me a lift,
I will definitely take it.
[Music]
Like falling deep
[Song sound][Music]
of [Music]
[Song sound] laughing
[Song sound][Music]
[Song sound]
[Music] Walking walking walking I
think
I'll get very skinny if I go on a trip to Goa.
Because I've been working a lot.   If
someone gives me a lift, I will definitely
take it.
Guys, someone gave me a lift.   The person who
gave me a lift today was also
from Maharashtra.
[singing voice][music]
I pack [music] myself some dinner lunch or
dinner whatever you call it 'cause I'm not gonna go
out today it's very very hot and I don't want to
read my skin
I [singing voice]
when we in the we can't we can do it we can do it I can't find
the miss
[music]
Good morning people it's a new day so let's say that it's
a beautiful day.  Today
is my day one like day three and day four here
in Goa.  I for to keep the track but or I'm
really having fun and I do
n't have any plans for today.  Today I think I will stay
in my room because I need to work.  I
need to do some shooting.  So I will complete that.
I guess.  But in the evening I may come here because
yesterday also I did not come.  And I was getting so much
FOMO.  I was thinking
I was in Goa.  Even after that I
am in the room.  Aisa feeling aa raha tha mere ko
[music]
million [music][song voice]
conversation
[song voice][music]
you you are more this
picture guys iss baari na
maine bahut crazy packing kiya hai.
Like I did pack a lot.  It was
packed so much that I had to carry two trolleys.
And I pack so
much because I thought I would make
so many contents.  You know
I will make so many videos like this.  And I missed
creating so much that I thought this time I will
create so much content.  I will create so much content.
So I just got ready to go
nowhere.  I'm gonna be filming some videos now.
I will film a hole video.  Thinking of
one or two.  And it is not raining too much in between.
So I don't know that
I will go anywhere today, not now.  I am very
grateful that I went in the morning.  But I will
try to go again because I do want to see
sunset and eat something and
not go to the beach.
So let's see.  Right now I will need at least two or
one hour to film this
video.  So I will see you all after
filming this video.  OK 3 hours later guys.
I just got done filming two
videos.  I need to edit also,
I will do the editing later.  I am not sure
weather, I should go out or not because it is a little
rainy season.  Well,
it is monsoon and it is going to be a rainy season.
But a little while ago it was raining heavily
and we stopped in between, then it rains again,
I am not sure.  But I will just get ready
you know because it is almost
sunset time.
I'm going I'm going [song voice]
Mujhe roke na koi I'm going I'm going I'm going
for dinner.  It is too early for
dinner but still I don't want
you to rush to eat later.  So I just want to enjoy,
I have been going through this route for three days.
But then I keep forgetting.
Okay, I have applied too much blush but
it's fine.  [Music] Okay.
[music]
yes [music] [song voice]
wait just a minute now what I do
to me [music]
yes [sing voice]
I do [music] to
wait a second take it slow wait say okay I'm a little
drunk right now so let me tell you all something that I did
n't think
I'd enjoy solo shrooms so much
man it's so fun I feel so
happy I feel so blessed I
feel so grateful
what is this life?  Oh my God.
[Song voice] So much to be
grateful for.  [screaming]
I love beaches, man.  I like the beach very much.  Too
much [music] too much.
too much too much too much.
Fun.   That's it
for today.
I need to leave for my BnB because I don't wanna be
late 10 on 10 experience dude
10 on 10 [music] go on solo date guys you're
going to love it if you're going to the beaches then do one thing if
[music] you love
beaches like me do one thing get your BnB a
little beach front so that it's
easier for you know because I love
beaches and [music] my take on this class trip was
I just wanna go near beaches walk
by the beaches [music] eat near the beaches and that's it.
I am covering my face.  I
Can See Some People Making Reels There and I Don't Wanna Come
In There [Music]
You Know Page.  Later mine will be coming in the For You page.
By the way [music] I think
so good guys.  10 on 10 I highly recommend
solo trip.
Fun.   Come on, I need to go.
I need to go but I don't really have to worry about whether
I will
reach safely or not.  Because it's only 2
minutes away.  There are not even 2 minutes left.  But that's where it's
fun.
Masti
[music]
Good morning guys.  It's a new day.  So let's just say that it's a
beautiful day.
I am having bread and coffee.  You guys might be wondering what happened to
Gom.  It's
11:3 AM and I just revealed that I bought a house.  Oh my
so excited.
You know I am having bread.  So the whole thing is
falling out of my hands.  Coffee Everything Is
Just Like Falling Off.   I'm
going crazy guys.  So sorry.  I will see you later.
Ok.  So it is 1:1 PM and I am going to get
ready to go to a cafe, new day, new cafe, this
is my Goa trip, I had told you all
earlier that I don't expect any touristy things
from my side, I thought I would go to
art galleries but they are very far
away, so I don't want to go, anyway I have
no interest in that, but I thought that I
can do a little bit of touristy things
but I don't have money and today my plan is to
go to a cafe.
I have seen a lot about that cafe in reels.
But I was not sure whether I should go
or not.  But someone has
personally recommended it to me.  So I am going to go there
dear.  Ok.  So let's get ready quickly.   First of all, I will
reapply sunscreen.   Ca
n't believe that I can tell you guys right now
that I am a home owner.  I have
bought a house.  Still can't believe it, man.  Every
time I think about this, I don't know that I have taken it home.
My Heart Skips a Bit Guys.  Like can't believe can't believe.
Can't Believe.  I hope you all have
such moments in your life that you can't
believe.  Can't believe moment.
Sorry guys, little too excited.  But you guys
can understand.  This was my only
dream.  Only dream.
Guys my outfit is so pretty like look
at this top it's raining again
so the top looks like this it is completely open
from the back you will have to tie like this that's the
reason I have also tied my hair and I have
my MirageO bag and inside it
I am wearing this one from Amazon it is
so soft like it is so stretchable and there is
lining inside also.  So you don't really have to worry about it
you know like a little see through all
this and underneath I am
wearing my black denim shs OG wala and
for footwear I am wearing this one from
theatre and that is it
ok
dinner time guys I am having spicy ramen
it is unhealthy but what to do I am
craving for something spicy and
and left over shim I don't have any
left over how will it be right now it won't be
crispy only or it will be soggy
but it is fine and also I was thinking of
extending my days in Goa.  I was
thinking that I am here only till the 31st
[sound of clearing throat] I have
booked this BnB till the 31st and I was thinking that
after that I will go to South Goa for maybe like
three to four days but no I am
craving for [laughs]
Rice Nagaland Thali so I am thinking
that I should go to Delhi.  So I'm having this yum
good afternoon guys.  It's a new day.  So let's just say that it's a
beautiful day.
It is 240 p.m.  And and you know what guys
I didn't eat anything yet.  And I feel like
eating something.  So I'm going to go to
this
cafe, restaurant, lunch.  I don't know.  Meaning
it's all in one.  I think I like
breakfast in the morning or something like that because
I have searched for these people and I don't
understand
what exactly they sell because I have
seen it on Zomato, they are selling like
sandwiches and all which I want to have it but
if I go and check out Instagram then they
sell drinks and all but whatever it is, I just want to have something
today I was thinking
that I should order food at home
because I did not feel like going out
but I was like no, I am going after two days,
what about tomorrow or the day after tomorrow, I think I am going there so I need to like enjoy
and another thing is I was thinking that
today I will go for a massage but I don't really have a
good experience with massage
because I have been to two times, one in Nepal and
one in Delhi and I did really like it I like
Urban Company massage like ghar me
bula ke massage that is better so I think I won't
go because  I am mentally preparing myself since yesterday
that I will go for
massage tomorrow but I don't know my heart and mind are
all saying that don't go so or I am not
going ok I am going to get ready now and I will also
film a reel I hope you guys are
watching my Instagram reels and all
because reels are done YouTube shots are done because I have been
filming a lot like
literally I have been filming so much so
still I will film my outfit
and then I will take you guys with me
new day new cafe open
[Music]
nice
love will happen.  [Song voice]
Going back to my BNB.  Today I am
not going to watch the sunset because baby should enjoy
because it is very cloudy like this,
so I will not get the sunset [music].
So that's it,
now here people are coming because it's sunset
time, but I am going to have so much
fun guys.  There's so much fun [music].  I
need to go on a solo trip again very soon.
So much fun, I had a lot of fun this trip.
My kind of fun.  You know what
guys?  Earlier, when
I used to go on tour, oh sorry,
I used to feel a lot of pressure that I need to show this
[music] and vlog that and vlog like this
and I was not able to enjoy
because I used to try to do touristy [music] stuff so
that you know, the vlogs look
interesting.  But as I'm growing older, I'm
realizing
that if I don't like it, I do
n't like it [the music].  Isn't it?  And there will be
some people who love to travel like me.
And you know like they will only be
attracted [music] to my channel.   So that's it.  I'm
Crossing Guys.  Crossing
Have An Update Guys.  I may not look sad right now but I am very very very
sad
because I have done something very stupid.
My trip was 10 on 10 until I rendered.   Yes.  Do you
know what I did guys?  I am so
stupid that I booked a
return ticket from Goa on 31st August and I
booked it from BNB, I have
also given the location here that I need a
taxi for the airport and taxis in Goa are very expensive
so it was around 2000 so
in total I have done something like 100800 and
I feel so stupid 100800 and this will not be refunded
also
I could have gone to Pilates yesterday only I was
thinking that I will go to Delhi and join Pilates.
I could have bought so many things with this
money.  I feel so bad.   I see it
in your eye.
[MUSIC]
Or I Can Read the Sign
Guys Look at My Outfit.  So pretty.
See tell you all
what my plans are for today.
I don't want to go out to be very honest
but I will regret it for sure.  So I'll just
go by the beach, walk by the beach, and then eat something
by the beach, and that's what they said.
So come on
[music] you need to get.
It's [music]
solo trip is fun until you have to ask
others to click pictures for you.  But you know
what?  I just saw a girl like she looks
very North Eastern.  So I asked him where are you from
?  She said she is
from Nagaland.  But I later
asked where she was from?  I ask her if you know can you
please click pictures of me
and she was like sure.  I said just keep pulling
, keep pulling, keep pulling and
she did exactly that.
Now I do have so many pictures.  I am
sure at least one or two good ones would have come.
And my plan for today was to ensure that my
phone's battery is fully charged.  Battery pura full
hoke I will just sit by the beach and you no
listen to music like this.  So I am doing exactly that.  The
weather is getting a little bad.
So I'm planning to go somewhere.  I am
not hungry.  So I may you know like walk by
the beach for a while.  After that I will go get something to eat.
Letts C.  I have seen a beautiful restaurant.
But I feel like I will need
to cross.  The entire place is within 8 minutes drive from here.  I don't mind
working.  So let's see.
[MUSIC]
I'M SO GRATEFUL.  I can't stop
romanticizing.  You know, whatever song I am listening to,
I am imagining myself in it.  I
have listened to a lot of music especially
Kaavish Taylor Swift and Atif Assalam.  Of
Course And There Are So Many Singers Like
Poora [Music] Mixed Songs.  You know I have also listened
to Keshi.  Like he is one of
those singers.  I used to listen to it a lot two-three years
ago.  I am listening to all the singers again.
And oh my god, it feels so good.
Surely I am going to miss this trip.  This
trip was so perfect.  Till I rendered
by booking ticket for 31st August but no one.
Whatever happens, happens for a reason.
Something must have happened for some reason.  Maybe Goa
wants me to see again, [music] wants me
to visit again.  Maybe Goa wants me to
settle here.  Hu Noz.  I don't want to settle here
but I
think I'm more of a city girl as I
love city life.
I hope you guys also go on a solo trip after
watching this video.  Trust me it's not that
bad.  You need to make it good.  You should
make this trip good for yourself.  And you
should travel the way you want to.  Like For
Me Traveling Is All About Food, Works and
You Know Beaches like Just Like That You Know I
love to slow travel.  So you guys can also do the way
you love so that your trip is memorable.
I was also planning to get a tattoo
but hm hm I am scared.  And I don't
want to be so impulsive.  By the way, I have been
thinking about getting a tattoo for
a very long time.  So I won't say this will be
impulsive also but I can't trust it.
And what I need today, I may
not need tomorrow.  [MUSIC] So I don't want like that,
you know, tattoos, so it's really
a big commitment.  Here are some things I
want you guys to take from me.
Romanticize everything like romanticize
literally everything if you listen to music
romanticize [music] that sad music
imagine yourself happy music imagine yourself
any music imagine yourself and
another thing is everything happens for a reason
if anything is happening in your life right now, good or bad everything happens
for a reason
and it is preparing you for something good
and what is yours will come to you in the right time
so don't worry about why is it not coming
to me
why is nothing good happening in my life [music]?
Because everything happens for a reason and when
it comes, it will come very well.  It will come
10 times better.  And be grateful for everything.
Because when you are grateful,
God will bless you even more.
And I am talking like this
without looking at the camera because I am
acting as if even I am on a video call so that
people do not think I am creepy.  But I don't
really worry about people now.  Go for a
solo trip guys.  Take my words you're
gonna love it.  You have to make it
interesting.  [MUSIC] You have to make it
fun.
Oh my god guys.  Oh my God.  I Met One of
You Guys and I For To Ask Her Name Is
Always Again.  Why do I forget to
ask your name?  But we had a really good
conversation.  She was saying that she [music]
watches my video you know while having
food like food.  Makes me so happy.  I ca
n't believe people from Goa also
watch my videos.  She was from Goa
only and
I was thinking that you know I will put a
story asking if anyone from Goa
wants to hang out like that but I didn't.
I think I should have done it.
I never thought that someone from Goa would
watch my video like this.  But none of
[music] I'm going tomorrow.  And it was
nice to meet you dear.
Oh my
ok guys it's drizzling [music] but
my heart is not agreeing to go to the BnB I
think it's my last day even if I get sick
it's fine I'm just gonna go by
the beach listen to some good music and you
no work for some time because because I am here I am here near
my BnB only
my BnB is just 2 minutes away from here
so I'm gonna listen to some music and
work by the beach this is life oh my god
anyway Goa's rain is like this only
one minute it's pouring [music] then the next
minute it stops raining so I think it's gonna be the same
today too and I might get drenched.  I don't
care.  I am very close to BNB.
I'm just gonna work two
rounds.
This is life, friend.  This is life.  Whenever I am
in my room, okay no I will overthink everything,
I will watch this vlog.  And I
will remind myself like Gom.  You just need
a trip.  You are doing good.  You need a trip
and a trip will fix you.  This is to
remind myself I will post this
video.
So I've been working by the beach
Romanticizing
so many songs I've heard Mostly sad
and I feel so grateful I don't know how to say goodbye I'm
crying I'm genuinely enjoying this trip so much
I had so much fun alone
Oh my god I don't know guys I'm feeling
so emotional
Trust me you need to go on a solo trip
Go it right now If you were thinking Because
I was also always like this You that solo
trip me kya hi mazaa bahut hoga Who will click
my pictures Strangers will even if
strangers don't click
selfies Take more than enough I did that My
whole trip And and if you feel like
how will you eat alone And all how will you
travel alone And all [Music] Trust me everything will happen
And once you start doing it It's
so addictive Like You will feel so good You will feel
so powerful You will
feel so good You will feel like Now no one can
hurt me You no like I  Can do anything and
everything alone you will get that feeling
trust me until next
time
bye thank you thank you for everything I will miss this
for sure I am going to miss this guys it's
11:30 pm I have done my skincare
and I am also done with my packing
and now I need to sleep but before that I thought I will do an
outro.  This trip was
really good and I had so much fun.  What I'm going to
say to you from this video is if [music]
you've been thinking about going on a solo
trip then you should because it was so much fun.   It was a
lot of fun.  And thank you so much for
watching till the end.  If you guys have watched
this video till here then comment this emoji.
And do let me know if I should make more of you know like
solo trip or trip wala vlog.
Because my usual thing is I don't really want to vlog
on Trip, but I think
I [music] should what you guys
think like do let me know in the comments
section.  Thank you so much for watching till the
end bye bye.  Love you.